## Jitendra Bordiya

Software Engineer in Jitendra.Bordiya

- Village-Kali Billod, INDORE, MADHYA PRADESH, 453001, India
- ± 07/1997 
  itendra7496@gmail.com +91 95168 82873

\*\*Having 2 yrs. of Experience as a NET Developer with Microsoft .NET Technologies in Asp. Net , MVC, C#, WCF Services, Web API, Net Core, MS SQL Server, Rest Services, Software Architecture. I am Actively looking for new opportunity that helps me to grow my technical skill that helps in the growth of organisation. \*\*

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Fendahl CTRM International

(11/2021 - Present)

Software Engineer

Contributed to Software design and development.

Diagnosed and resolved database defects, ensuring QA deployment stability.

Gathered development requirements, created physical data models, and designed database schema.

Debugged and fixed bugs in the existing project.

Conducted Unit Testing and participated in code reviews.

Thinkquotient Software Pvt Ltd

(08/2021 - 11/2021)

.NET Intern

Employee Appraisal System: Employee Appraisal System is a Console Based Application Which contains database of a Company Employee and Monitoring employee Performance and Appraisal History and Perform CRUD operation on Employee Information for ex. Add a new employee, Retreive Employee Information, Update Employee Information, Delete Existing Employee. Tech Tools: C#, SQL Server 2018, ADO.NET, Visual Studio 2019, Console App, GitHub.

https://fendahl.com/

## **EDUCATION**

 ${\bf Sagar\ Institute\ of\ Research\ \&\ Technology\ Excellence,}$ Ayodhya Bypass Road, Bhopal -462041

Sanskar Academy High Secondary School

(07/2015 - 07/2016)

Bachelor of Engineering - BE

(01/2016 -01/2020)

HSC, Science

64%

**PROJECTS** 

Pokemon Review APP

(06/2023)

Word Counter - APP

(06/2023 - 06/2023)

Pokémon Review API is a Web Api

Pokémon review App is a Web Api which shows Pokémon details and owner information etc we can Add, update, delete and retrieve information. Technology and Tools:.NET Core 7 Web API, C#, SQL Server 2018, AutoMapper, JWT Bearer for Authentication, JSON, Visual Studio

Word Counter is a React App

Word Counter is an app that count word in an article, Average read time, word preview and clear text screen, upper and lower case conversion of article. Technology: ReactJs, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, HTML5.CSS3

https://github.com/JitendraBordiya/ReactJs-WordsCounter

https://github.com/JitendraBordiya/Pokemon-Review-APP

**SKILLS** 

.NET Framework **ASP.NET Core ASP.NET MVC** ASP.NET Web API

Windows Communication Foundation (WCF)

HTML5

C# Microsoft SQL Server

**Entity Framework (EF Core) Object-Oriented Programming** 

(OOP)

**JSON jQuery** 

**REST APIs** React.js Visual Studio **JavaScript** 

Git Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

**CERTIFICATIONS** 

**SOL** Certificate SOL (intermediate) (12/2021)(12/2021)

HackerRank

HackerRank https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/dfbd25b379af

https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/b9dc914a8d18

(01/2022)

Problem Solving (Basic)

HackerRank

https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/d7f6cfcd67be